[Music] you
[Música]
know but well I think that little by little
sabes pero bueno Yo creo que poco a poco
you care that you want to upload four or
te importa que quieres subir cuatro o
five minutes Javi Speaking clearly to give your
cinco minutos Javi Hablando claro para
opinion on Jorge man but since it's not that
opinar algo de Jorge hombre pero como no
I care it's that he uploads it already it's that I
es que me importe es que que suba ya
wasn't looking at WhatsApp
es que no estaba mirando el WhatsApp
because when I'm live these
porque cuando estoy en directo estos
days and especially if I'm with someone I
días y sobre todo si estoy con alguien
put it on airplane mode Forgive me Javi
lo pongo en modo avión Perdóname Javi
nothing well about the issue that sounds
nada bien por el tema de que suena por
here in the microphone like a
aquí en el micrófono como una
strange interference and such that I still haven't
interferencia rara y tal que todavía no
seen Antonio's entire live
me he visto el directo entero de Antonio
now come on because I still haven't seen
ahora sube que todavía no me visto el
Antonio's entire live because he
directo entero de Antonio porque me
told me the thing I was watching the
contó la movida he estado viendo la
part about me wanting the chicha de la
parte de que yo quería la chicha de la
chicha and I was watching a little of what he
chicha y estuve viendo un poco lo que
said about Olga and now when
dijo de Olga y ahora cuando ya se vaya
Javi leaves we're going to want to comment on a
Javi vamos a quiero comentar unas
few things from there because on the one
cuantas de cosas de ahí porque por un
hand Antonio David said something very
lado Antonio David dijo una cosa muy
nice
bonita
and I don't know if yesterday's interview with
y no sé yo si la entrevista de ayer de
Marta with charisma could have had
Marta con carismán pudo haber tenido
some element that overshadowed
algún elemento que le hiciera sombra
some of the nice things that
alguna de las cosas bonitas que dijo
Antonio David said and intentionally
Antonio David e intencionadamente
because it came out because it didn't come out or whatever
porque le salió porque no le salió o lo
but
que sea pero
now now  we'll go into depth
ahora ahora entraremos en profundidad
but look, I don't
pero fíjate tú que a mí es que no me cae
dislike Marta you know, I mean like I
mal Marta sabes o sea en plan A mí
don't either
tampoco
Look at Marta's problem well
Mira el problema de Marta bueno problema
no problem Simply what I think is happening to her
no Simplemente yo lo que creo que le
is that she is totally indignant
pasa es que está totalmente indignada
because she feels that she doesn't have the same
porque siente que ella no tiene el mismo
place for example that Olga had in terms of
lugar por ejemplo que tenía Olga de Cara
the opinion of the followers of the
a la opinión a los seguidores de la
tide I think that is what
marea yo creo que eso es lo que le
bothers her because she no longer understands that a
molesta porque ya no entiende que una
person who loves so much the person that
persona que quiere tanto a la persona
everyone defends is being
que todos defienden se la esté
criticized so much you know and it's like she sees
criticando tanto sabes y es como que ve
that Olga is loved and has been loved a
que Olga se la quiere y se le ha querido
lot and it doesn't surprise me Because for me she is
mucho y no me extraña Porque para mí es
a wonderful woman each
una mujer estupenda cada una lección
television lesson of what it is to be a lady and
televisiva de lo que es ser una señora y
she feels like she doesn't have that space
ella siente como que no tiene ese hueco
and as if she claims it and as if she can't
y como que lo reivindica y como que no
have in Newcomer there were
puede tener en Recién llegada hubo
several indications at the beginning she had several
varios indicios al principio tuvo varias
that now we enter wait to see if you
que ahora entramos espérate a ver si
go up there Okay, well I want this
subes ahí Vale pues quiero que este
extract to be complete perfect
extracto sea completo perfecto
half an hour eh Look at WhatsApp Look at
media hora eh Mira WhatsApp Mira
WhatsApp so you can see it I was
WhatsApp para que veas tú lo estaba
watching it Look it's here
viendo Mira está aquí
Javi What's up son Forgive me it's that I
Javi Qué pasa hijo Perdóname que es que
put the mobile You know that  this is your
pongo el móvil Tú sabes que esta es tu
house you can come in here like if you
casa que tú puedes entrar aquí como si
want to upload video all here but the one
quiere subir vídeo todo aquí pero que la
I put the phone in airplane mode Well
que pongo el móvil modo avión Pues
because I don't know why there's
porque no sé porque suenan
interference and since I'm with Marina
interferencias y como estoy con Marina
so I hadn't seen it let's go because I've already
por lo no lo había visto vamos porque lo
seen it because Échame I was
he visto ya porque Échame lo estaba
warning you what's up laugh Good night how are you
avisando que pasa reír Buenas noches qué
Marina can you hear me well it's
tal Marina me escucháis bien
not that what's happening is that I'm working
no es que lo que pasa que estoy currando
and I escaped there for 10 or 15 minutes
y me he escapado ahí 10 o 15 minutos
because I'm biting my nails I
porque me estoy mordiendo las uñas los
have them in radio mode
tengo en modo radio
and it's I'm biting my nails okay It's that I
y es estoy mordiendo las uñas vale Es
really see a montage
que yo yo de verdad yo veo un montaje
very clearly very clearly I mean there are
clarísimo pero clarísimo o sea es que
many things that really bother me I mean
hay muchas cosas que a mí de verdad O
first the girl is Alicia his
sea primero la chica está Alicia a su
wife I think she's making a
mujer yo creo que está haciendo el
fool of herself on social media I mean I know that there are
papelón en redes o sea yo sé que hay
many people because they've left me in
mucha gente que porque me han dejado en
comments that they've made a
comentarios que se me han hecho un
little bit of me because today Poor thing
poquito encima porque hoy Pobrecita
because she's the poor thing But anyway
porque es la pobrecita Pero bueno lo
first I'm not spoiling your fun No
primero no os estoy cortando el rollo No
because I know it's Tuesday with Marina and
porque yo sé que es martes con Marina y
we're not entering right now
tampoco estamos entrando ahora mismo
before the preliminaries
antes de los preliminares
Because look what she commented about
Porque mira lo que ha comentado de
frigente And the thing is that frigenti I have her as
frigente Y es que frigenti le tengo como
a not very credible person but it is
una persona poco creíble pero sí que es
true that she is looking for a
cierto que es que está como buscando un
lot of notoriety in networks on
montón de notoriedad en redes en
Instagram that she is dedicated to being a
instagram que ella se dedica a hacer
coach of these of you know not of
coach de estos de ya sabes no de
personal growth and such And she is
crecimiento personal y tal Y está
focusing this problem on
enfocando este problema al crecimiento
personal growth and that is to generate well what
personal y eso es para generar pues lo
all that on the one hand and then when
que todo eso por un lado y luego cuando
Marina says that what they gain is that
Marina dice que qué salen ganando es que
they I maybe I am very bad thinking
ellos Yo a lo mejor soy muy mal pensado
with these people but I think that they have
con esta gente pero yo creo que les han
told them Hey look the red issue is over
dicho Oye mira se ha acabado el tema
this has to be lifted And this is
rojito esto hay que levantarlo Y esto es
what there is do you accept Because it is a lot of
lo que hay aceptáis Porque es que mucha
coincidence Marina and Javi that [ __ ] just
casualidad Marina y Javi que [__] justo
ends that issue and just this Boom
termina ese tema y justo este Boom
talking about it all over Mediaset Even in
hablándolo por todo mediaset Incluso en
Ana Rosa's program that is from
el programa de Ana Rosa que sí que es de
the same producer and such And it
la misma productora y tal Y me parece
all seems very I don't know very very cooked everything you
todo muy no sé muy muy cocinado todo
know to me an aside to me The only thing that
sabéis a mí un inciso a mí Lo único que
puts me off and what makes me
me echa para atrás y de que me hace
think that it is not a montage is that this
pensar que no es un montaje es que esta
lady Alicia just had a child
señora Alicia acaba de tener un hijo
four months ago at what point you with
hace cuatro meses en qué momento tú con
a newborn child that you are almost
un hijo recién nacido que casi le estás
Well almost no, I'm not a mother but let's say you
Bueno casi no yo no soy madre pero vamos
're breastfeeding at what point do
que le estás amamantando en qué momento
you stop to think or agree you agree
te paras a pensar o accedes accedes a
that publicly you are seen as the
Que públicamente quedes como la
humiliated one of Spain and on top of that on social
humillada de España y encima además en
media you gloat and upload stories
redes Te regodeas y subes historias
stories stories like like the like
historias historias en plan como como la
the martyr it's that they are like attitudes
como la mártir es que son como actitudes
that I I
que yo
think the same as you the issue of the
Yo pienso lo mismo que tú el tema del
child let's see clearly okay you can make a
niño a ver claro vale tú puedes hacer un
montage with a thousand things okay but man
montaje con mil cosas vale pero hombre
when we're talking about a
cuando estamos hablando Ya de un
marriage there are four children no like that it's
matrimonio son cuatro hijos no así es
not about the baby anymore that she has
que ya no se trata del bebé que tiene
another three even if they
otros tres aunque no sean bebé quiere
are not babies she wants to look like a cuckold that on TV it is that your father cheated on your mother but that but but you say that because because we are people with values ​​Maybe because it's that I tell you one thing her father came out this afternoon on Sálvame
ha salido su padre esta tarde en sálvame
there they are They are already preparing the
allá están Ya están preparando el
ground
terreno
her father came out Sálvame today
salió su padre sálvame hoy ha salido
something like a God came out that I don't want to
algo así como un Dios que no lo quiero
say it Eh but in a
decir Eh pero en plan
closed way my goodness it came out well sorry sorry no no sorry sorry
cerrado madre mía ha salido bueno perdón
Marina no no
perdón no no perdón perdón Marina no no
no that he made some statements that it
no que ha hecho unas declaraciones que
is very so much but I  I
es que es muy tanta pero yo le he
understood him but I know that people will have
entendido pero yo sé que la gente habrá
said that he is sexist because it is
dicho que machista porque sí que es
true that he blames indirectly as he
verdad que culpa indirectamente como
puts the focus he is saying that he has been caught
pone en foco está diciendo la han cazado
and the one who is very expert in this has
y el que es muy experto en esto se ha
let himself be caught and well that they have not gone to
dejado cazar y bueno que no se han ido a
bed you know that they have not done a kiki and it
la cama sabes que no han hecho un kiki y
is like in plan Well
es como en plan Bueno
the second thing I was going to tell you is that they have
lo segundo que te iba a decir que han
dropped the bombshell that also comes from
soltado el bombazo que viene también de
frigen and that we have to take it with a thousand
frigen y que hay que cogerlo con mil
tweezers that the party ended at 4
pinzas de que se acabó la fiesta a las 4
in the morning Jorge arrived at 6 because he
de la mañana Jorge llegó a las 6 porque
went to Marta López's house to finish
se fue a casa de Marta López a terminar
the heat he said that distressingly
el calentón eso lo ha soltado afligente
and half of sálvame of course is valid you have to
y mitad de sálvame claro es vigente hay
take it with tweezers later
que cogerlo con pinzas después
let's see another girl came out of the
vamos a ver ha salido otra chica de la
party I don't remember her name who
fiesta que no recuerdo su nombre que se
approached them when they were flirting
ha acercado cuando estaban con el tonteo
at the beginning as soon as the
al principio nada más empezar las
parties started she approached because she gets along well with
fiestas se acercó porque se va bien con
Jorge she said to him Hey man You're at a
Jorge le dijo Oye tío Estás en una
party with 500 journalists everyone is
fiesta con 500 periodistas todos están
watching Maria
mirando María
cut it out man Why not no get out of
córtate tío Porque tal no no quítate de
here and apparently Alba the  He grabbed her and
aquí y por lo visto Alba la cogió la
said rudely get out of here you know
dijo de malas formas vete de aquí sabes
then yesterday saying that in the
luego ayer diciendo que en el chat del
guasch chat in his WhatsApp
guasch en el WhatsApp suyo
group that everyone Ah look what's
del grupo que todos Ah mira lo que está
happening look what's happening and
pasando mira lo que está pasando y dijo
she said Of course it's recorded badly
ella Claro está mal grabada la
colleagues but if the producer sees it
compañeros pero si la productora lo ve
well and says go ahead then go
bien y dice para adelante pues para
ahead and then you want to sell me I'm
adelante y luego me quieres vender ya
done and I'll shut up but you want to
termino y me callo pero me quieres
sell me that you act like a long-suffering Emma
vender que te haces la sufrida Emma
García saying how are we going to get photos
García diciendo cómo vamos a sacar fotos
of Rafa Mora that drunk that
de Rafa Mora que borracho que eso le
can happen to anyone in the
puede pasar a cualquier persona en el
world made a show all day about how I'm
mundo hizo un show el día entero de cómo
going to get the photo of Rafa mora
voy a sacar la foto de Rafa morada
drunk that is going to damage his image
borracho eso va a dañar su imagen
Poor thing and you sell Jorge López
Pobrecito y vendes a Jorge López
marriage four children
matrimonio cuatro hijos
please let's
por favor
see I think it's that you know I am
a ver yo creo que es que sabes a mí me
surprised that it was Jorge Pérez in
sorprende que haya sido Jorge Pérez en
this case
este caso
in the end López Pérez what kills himself
al final López Pérez qué mata el mismo
no but
no pero
Total yes it is true that what
Total que sí que es verdad que a mí lo
surprises me is that in the case of
que me sorprende es que en el caso de
being a strategy also on the part of
ser una estrategia también por parte de
the network that The Chosen One is Jorge Pérez
la cadena que El Elegido sea Jorge Pérez
because I want to tell you let's understand each other it is
porque te quiero decir entendámonos está
very good very good to look at but it is not it is not It's that I do
muy bien de muy buen ver pero no es no
not want to make a comparison
es Es que no quiero hacer comparativa
with another Julio drones type
con otro Julio drones tipo
Of course there They had a charisma a something
Claro que ahí Tenían un carisma un algo
television but in this case he has
televisivo pero en este caso él ha dicho
also said on his social networks that let's see
además en sus redes sociales que a ver
if he fulfills it that he is not going to speak
si lo cumple que no se va a pronunciar
more on this matter and and that with this
más sobre este asunto y y que con el
statement that he put out last
comunicado este que puso ayer por la
night with this everything is clear
noche que con esto todo quedó claro
So he is closing ranks I am
Entonces él está cerrando fila me
surprised that now what is being sought are
sorprende que ahora lo que se busca es
Jorge's words after
las palabras de Jorge a raíz de que de
fringe has commented that there was more than
fringente ha comentado que hubo más que
that they put out the fire together at
que apagaron el fuego junticos en casa
Marta López's house I am surprised that Jorge
de Marta López me sorprende que Jorge
tomorrow in already another day or the day after that he will go does
mañana en ya otro día o pasado que irá
not talk about the subject he has assured it So I
no hable del tema él lo ha asegurado
think I know how
Entonces yo creo que sé cómo funciona
this works I sense that the introducer is going to
esto intuyo que la introductora se lo va
impose it we are going to put a gun but
a imponer vamos a poner una pistola pero
of course if when they want to tell you if
claro si cuando se te quiere decir si
many times you are a little not for decoration
muchas veces estás un poco no de adorno
but contributing it just right now that it is your
pero aportandolo justito ahora que es tu
moment We want to get a cut but I don't
momento Queremos sacar de tajada pero no
know how Jorge is going to react so clear
sé cómo va a reaccionar Jorge tan claro
that he has to that this no no you you and it is that I
que tiene que que esto no no tú tú y es
have little time you you what creates
que tengo poco tiempo tú tú qué te crea
more expectation for a scoundrel acting the
más expectación a un golfo haciendo el
Scoundrel or a person who is going to get out of it
Golfo o una persona que se la va a salir
morality doing and breaking his
de la moralidad haciendo y rompiendo su
word what Moro believes more and what
palabra qué crea más Moro y que crea más
the second one believes more spectacular Of course of course
espectacular lo segundo Claro claro
but well he is wrong of course
pero bueno está equivocado por supuesto
I do not have the truth we cannot affirm
yo no tengo la verdad no podemos afirmar
anything at the moment at the moment there is no you can
nada de momento de momento no hay puedes
believe And you can have an indication based on it
creer Y puedes tener indicio en base
you know but to affirm no we do not have something
sabes pero afirmar no no tenemos algo
shameless we do not have something shameless but
descarado no tenemos algo descarado pero
we are overlooking one thing And that
nos estamos pasando por alto una cosa Y
is that when Miguel, I knowing Alba
es que cuando Miguel yo conociendo Alba
and when Miguel said this afternoon
y cuando Miguel ha dicho esta tarde
Jorge went to mom's house
Jorge fue a casa de mamá
dad upstairs
papá arriba
through someone well wherever and we do not
a través de alguien bueno donde sea y no
know anything about this matter he has not
sabemos nada de este tema no se ha
spoken with me
pronunciado ni conmigo
about the house
lo de la casa
yes when frigenti said this
sí que cuando frigenti ha dicho esta
afternoon that Jorge Pérez after the
tarde que Jorge Pérez después de la
party went to Marta López's house to
fiesta fue a casa de Marta López a
put out the fire with Alba Carrillo that I do
apagar el fuego con Alba Carrillo que yo
not know how Alba Carrillo was seeing
no sé cómo estaría Alba Carrillo viendo
the situation in conditions I mean
el percal en condiciones me refiero
when I said that knowing Alba
cuando he dicho eso conociendo Alba
Carrillo Alba the minute I said that If it
Carrillo Alba al minuto de decir eso Si
is not true I would have
no es cierto hubiera lo hubiera
denied it like crazy or on networks or
desmentido como una loca o en redes o en
equally both
igual tanto
that non-confirmation sounds like it or I mean that
esa no confirmación me suena o sea ese
non-denial sounds like confirmation to me you
no desmentido me suena confirmación
know anyway let's imagine one thing is that
sabes total vamos imagínate una cosa es
I there with Marta  López, you are not going to
que yo ahí a Marta López yo no te van a
find her, far from it, but
encontrar de ella ni mucho menos pero
with all due respect, I believe that Marta López
con todo respeto creo que Marta López no
is not a trustworthy person as a friend, both
es una persona de fiar como amiga tanto
in this case and in many things
tanto en este caso como en muchas cosas
with Olga Moreno, I have realized that she is
con Olga Moreno me he dado cuenta que es
a person who may approach you
una persona que puede que se te acerque
to try to get something from you, like
por intentar conseguir algo de ti en
how to raise in Olga's case,
plan que como subir en el caso de Olga
I see it as if she wants to present herself as a female
yo veo como que quiere dársela de mujer
friend of Olga, in order to raise her prestige a little,
amiga de Olga como para subir un poco su
her cache as a collaborator
prestigio su caché de colaboradora que
there, I have contact with Olga and she uploads
hay tengo contacto con Olga y sube
stories with them, she records I don't know what. In
historias con ellas graba no sé qué De
fact, she didn't use it, she put me in a
hecho no usaba me la puso en un
difficult position because she almost even recorded it
compromiso porque casi incluso la graba
while on vacation and in Elche, I
estando de vacaciones y en elche yo le
see it as an attitude in the
veo como una actitud en las historias de
Instagram stories as if she wants to record to
Instagram como que quiere grabar para
catch them and for it to be uploaded. Instagram,
pillarlos y que se suba Instagram el
karaf turns me on Marina,
karaf me pone marina
I'll tell you one thing. I think that
que yo te digo una cosa Yo pienso que a
Marta being friends with Olga has
Marta ser amiga de Olga le ha
harmed her, she has given her more days
perjudicado le ha dado cabida más días
when the subject was going to be discussed, but the
cuando se iba a tratar el tema pero el
public ridicule that has been made of
escarnio público que se ha hecho con
her with Marta Flores, as
ella con Marta flores como la llama la
people call her, I think has not benefited her on an
gente yo creo que no le ha beneficiado a
image level  I think I think and then I'll tell you something else
nivel imagen creo Creo y luego te digo
what he said what do you
otra cosa lo que ha dicho el qué tú
think that no like he defended her very
crees que no en plan la defendió muy
well on vacation in fact I
bien en unas vacaciones de hecho me
remember the survivor for example
acuerdo el superviviente por ejemplo la
Marta defended her better than Luque
defendía mejor Marta que la gana Luque
who was the one who had to defend her you know
que era la que tenía que defender sabes
but well it's an impression eh I mean I
pero bueno es una impresión eh o sea
'm not telling you either
tampoco te estoy diciendo
I agree with you
estoy de acuerdo contigo
on the phone Let's see you upload stories
en el móvil A ver tú tú subes historias
being at a party with your friends and all that
estando de fiesta con tus amigos y todo
stuff about your stories she's a bit silly whatever
eso de tus historias hace un poco tonto
but she's like that like that you know a
lo que sea pero ella es así así sabes un
bit the disco I knew it's like she gave me
poco la discoteca sabía es como me dio
the impression that she wanted to catch them you don't
la impresión de que quería cogerlos no
get the impression No but if just
te da la impresión No pero si justo
when the recording is being done there are
cuando se está grabando el el que es hay
several no but the one that is more the one
varios no pero el que es más
that comes out Marta López okay she looks out
el que sale Marta López vale ella Mira
of the corner of her eye and which one is that you see as
de reojo y en cual es que se ve en
soon as she sees that Alba Carrillo is on top
cuanto ve que Alba Carrillo está encima
of Jorge She turns the camera and that's when
de Jorge Gira la cámara y es cuando
Jorge separates and starts pretending to
Jorge se separa y se pone a hacer como
sing Well that would be an indication of
que canta Pues eso sería un indicio de
not editing more than editing I would say I do
no montaje más que de montaje yo diría
n't know I don't know
No lo sé No lo sé
and another thing Sorry to change the subject for a second
y otra cosa Perdón que cambie un segundo
regarding what
de tema que respecto a lo que ha contado
Miguel said today sorry that  come back to this topic that
hoy Miguel de perdón que vuelva el tema
Alba that Jorge would have
este de que Alba de que Jorge habría
paid for that fire with Alba at
pues te ha pagado ese fuego con Alba en
Marta López's house, you know what
casa de Marta López sabes a mí lo que me
makes me put it good or put it in doubt or
hace ponerlo bueno o ponerlo en duda o
not put it in doubt in the end Miguel carries
no ponerlo en duda al final Miguel lleva
or if you have noticed he carried an earpiece
o si os habéis fijado llevaba pinganillo
that he usually always carries and there is
que lo suele llevar siempre y no hay
nothing like having a good earpiece which
nada como tener un buen pinganillo que
can be the best I want to tell you that
puede ser lo mejor te quiero decir que
the fact that the earpiece arrives I don't
el hecho de que llegue pinganillo yo no
know if it is more of a guideline
sé si es más un poco una directriz
understand me on my part it is that I don't know how to
entendedme por parte es que no sé cómo
explain it let's see how I explain it
explicarlo a ver cómo lo explico
but that would not fit me being unique and
pero no me cuadraría eso al ser único y
the television factory
la fábrica de la tele
but look at one thing that is both unique and
pero fíjate una cosa que tanto único
unique as the television factory
tanto único como la fábrica de la tele
is dealing with this subject that I thought that
Está tratando este tema que yo pensé que
the factory was not going to deal with it because it was
la fábrica no lo iba a tratar porque era
such a unique origin in all its splendor
tan origen único en todo su esplendor
that I thought that it was not going to deal with it eh You
que pensé que no lo iba a tratar eh
only have to see the audiences
Solo hay que ver las audiencias
on YouTube they are having, I mean you can see
en YouTube están teniendo o sea se nota
that it is a subject like
que es un tema como
people are super hooked on the subject
la gente está súper enganchada al tema
because I tell you it is like Jorge López,
porque te digo es como Jorge López el
Rocío Flores' friend, he is an
amigo de Rocío flores el Es guardia
exemplary civil guard with a
civil modélico con una moralidad
superior morality  family four children that's
superior familia cuatro hijos eso
addictive but what I wanted to tell you about
engancha pero lo que te quería decir de
Miguel frigentillo I think is that he
Miguel frigentillo creo yo es que lo
took it with super clamp
cogió con super pinza
something more has to come out for me to
tiene que salir algo más para que yo me
believe it but but I think If it's not
lo crea pero pero yo creo Si no es
true he said it because Miguel and he can't
verdad lo ha soltado porque Miguel y no
stand what's her name what's the
soporta a Cómo se llama cómo se llama la
little girl's name this door the journalist
chiquita esta puerta la periodista
Carmen Porta not Cristina Porta the door
Carmen Porta no Cristina Porta la puerta
No no it's that what I was going to tell you that he ca
No no es que lo que te iba a decir que
n't stand Cristina contributes and
no soporta Cristina aporta y por lo
apparently Cristina Porta is very much with
visto Cristina Porta está muy a tope con
Jorge Pérez and Jorge Pérez very much with
Jorge Pérez y Jorge Pérez muy a tope con
Cristina Porta is that he has even said
Cristina Porta es que ha llegado a decir
that Jorge Pérez is voseaba for Cristina
que Jorge Pérez va voseaba por Cristina
Polo that I did say that's why in the end
Polo eso sí lo he dicho por eso al final
friggente and it has credibility because
friggente y tiene credibilidad porque
Look listening to one thing in the end I
Mira escuchando una cosa al final Yo
understand that you might do it
entiendo que vosotros igual lo hacéis a
Well this one
Bueno Este
this one He can't stand this one etc But the
esta No soporta este etc Pero es que yo
truth is that I am telling you not to believe anything
de verdad os digo que no os creáis nada
because it's all television and just like
porque todo es televisión y al igual que
you see on a plate that then
veis en un plato que luego se toman
everyone has a coffee okay leaving out
todos un café vale quitando casos
specific cases but what I want to tell you
concretos pero que te quiero decir
that each one in fact I was
que cada uno de hecho a mí me ha
surprised that Miguel defended between
sorprendido que Miguel defendiese entre
quote marks  to Alba because Well it's not that I was
comillas a Alba porque Bueno no es que
surprised but that they didn't end
me haya sorprendido sino que no acabaron
very well they had a bad relationship Then it
muy bien tenía mala relación Luego
seems that things got better a little
parece que la cosa se arregló un poquito
and yes, the truth is that I was surprised that she
y sí que me ha sorprendido la verdad que
defends Alba's position But well, if it is
defienda la postura de Alba Pero bueno
that way of account and that these two have
que de ser así de cuenta y que estos dos
had all this, one is
hayan tenido todo esto uno
because of Alba's attitude that knowing
esa por la actitud de Alba que sabiendo
what has happened if that has happened
lo que ha pasado si es que eso ha pasado
Alba has not told it publicly
Alba no lo haya contado públicamente
because that Yes so much yes so much is
porque eso Si tanto si tanto lo está
doing it for benefit Alba would have
haciendo por beneficio Alba lo hubiera
told it not to generate more plot she
contado no para generar más trama ella
for the moment has not told it he has
de momento no lo ha contado él
been and she believes him So I do
ha habido y ella le crea a él Entonces
n't know but you generate more plot you know
no sé pero generas más trama sabes
you stretch the gum more if you do it little by
estiras más el chicle si lo vas poco a
little I mean if right now Alba Carrillo
poco o sea si ahora mismo Alba Carrillo
with the isler that she has suddenly explodes
con el isler que tiene explota de
even she herself has said it It's that
repente hasta ella mismo lo ha dicho Es
then you say that Alba explodes if she
que luego decís que Alba explota si ella
explodes suddenly she will be left like the one
explota de repente va a quedar como la
who suddenly explodes once again Alba
que explota de repente una vez más Alba
Carrillo But if she already acts like she
Carrillo Pero si ya hace la que se
holds it in and she is stretching it out little by little
aguanta y se va estirando poquito a poco
and the thing is that I have reached my limit because
y es que he llegado a mi límite porque
Jorge Pérez is talking badly about me behind my
Jorge Pérez está hablando mal de mí a
back because this because the other
las espaldas porque esto porque lo otro
I'll tell you one thing, change her, Carlón. I do
yo te digo una cosa cambiarla carrillón
n't like her at all. I'll say it right now, the one who is
No me cae nada bien que lo digo desde ya
least to blame, I mean, if this
la que menos culpa tiene o sea si esto
isn't a montage. This isn't a montage. And
no es un montaje Esto no es un montaje Y
this is true, which I doubt. But well,
esto es verdad que yo lo dudo Pero bueno
if it's true, the only thing that
si es verdad aquí lo único que se le
can be thrown in Alba Carrillo's face here is, Hey,
puede echar en cara Alba Carrillo es Oye
girl, how do you get married men in? What's
tía Cómo Entras hombres casados no que
up with your thing, the scale of values,
pasa con tu rollo la escala de valores
but she is free in terms of values. But
pero ella es libre a nivel de valores
one thing, one thing is honestly
pero una cosa una cosa es sinceramente
where Alba Carrillo is going to explode because,
dónde va a explotar Alba Carrillo porque
well, maybe at a party, because let's see
bueno igual en fiesta porque a ver
Unicor, for example, the most at the
unicor en por ejemplo el más en la
TV factory, on Sálvame, on Saturday
fábrica de la tele en sálvame el sábado
of light, etc., it's a program in which we have
de luz etc es un programa en el que
seen Alba at her best,
hemos visto Alba en su máximo esplendor
in her absolute madness, so
en su desquicia absoluto entonces
midday is not a program of that style
mediodía no es un programa de ese estilo
and there is a line and it can't go out and you can't
y hay una línea y no te puede salir y no
raise hell, now at
puedes montar el pollo padren ya medio
midday because you won't come back the next day,
día porque no vuelves al día siguiente
and now this and this detail, and now you
y ahora esto y este detalle y ahora la
already know the house.
casa ya las sabes
No, Jorge is not going to take her to Sálvame, it's
no no la va a llevar Jorge a sálvame es
that he's a man, Alicia, no, but not for nothing,
que es hombre Alicia no pero no por nada
but because you already know what happened with
sino porque ya sabéis lo que pasó con
Jorge and Alba.  and his mother too of
Jorge y Alba y su madre también
course we know but I'll tell you one
claro que lo sabemos pero yo te digo una
thing
cosa
Yes yes the network imposes it for
Sí sí la cadena se lo impone por tema
audience reasons no matter what Jorge says I'll tell you
audiencia por mucho que diga Jorge te lo
Well I'll
digo yo Bueno
tell you and Jorge swallows it I'll
te lo digo yo y Jorge se lo traga te lo
tell you yes of course exactly
digo yo sí claro exactamente
but it would be hard for me now to think about
pero a mí me costaría ahora pensar a
Álvaro de Luz I can't imagine it because it
Álvaro de luz no me la imagino porque le
could be going very well for him because that day he could
puedo ir muy bien porque ese día puede
earn 15,000 20,000 euros but I don't know
ganar 15.000 20.000 euros pero yo no sé
to what extent this image he had
hasta qué punto la imagen esta que había
managed to adopt Although some
conseguido adoptar Aunque algunos la
criticize her I don't understand why we like it
critiquen yo no entiendo que nos gusta
Of course but in the end the fact that she
Claro pero al final el hecho de que se
positions herself with Rocío Carrasco because she
posicione de Rocío Carrasco porque la
makes her look like [ __ ] for many I don't
convierte en una [__] para muchos no
understand it's
lo entiendo
not about what you think it's about what she
no se trata de lo que tú pienses se
is husband because you
trata de lo que es marida porque ya
know that this issue has divided everyone
sabes que este tema ha dividido todo
but how could I not know that it has divided
pero cómo no voy a saber que ha dividido
if I imagine
si a mí me imagino
Carrasco who are very valid eh to me for
Carrasco que son muy válidas eh a mí por
example Paloma García Pelayo she
ejemplo Paloma García Pelayo a mí me
seems like a very valid journalist to me She is very
parece una periodista muy válida Es muy
professional Paloma Barrientos
profesional Paloma Barrientos
Of course of course
Claro claro
seriously because I'm starting to
a seriedad porque es que yo empiezo a
be No  not because of you but I'm starting to get
estar No no por vosotros pero yo empiezo
a little tired of people who
a estar un poco cansada que la gente que
maybe an example people who are like
a lo mejor un ejemplo gente que es así
more fun more chatty and
como más divertida más de charachera y
then tell their things it seems that since they
luego cuenta sus cosas parece que como
are not the typical older serious person
no es la típica persona más mayor seria
who tells everything like with it seems
que lo cuenta todo así como con parece
that the appearance Even gives you more
que el aspecto Incluso te da como más
credibility
credibilidad
for me palomar that Pelayo despite the fact that he
para mí palomar ese Pelayo a pesar de
has made me black many times in
que me ha puesto negro muchas veces en
the subject of Rocío Carrasco for me he won
el tema de Rocío Carrasco para mí ganó
a point on the night of Pepe Navarro and
un puntazo en la noche de Pepe Navarro y
he had balls men that thanks to
le echó [__] hombres que gracias a
her unleashed man total he
ella desencadenó hombre total
did that for image I think eh then he
eso lo hizo por imagen yo creo eh luego
returned or he did not return to the deluxe
volvió o no volvió al deluxe
I have not seen more pigeons in the
yo no hemos visto más a palomas en la
brand
marca
I had to give in I don't know what they did in
he tenido que ceder no sé qué hicieron
the afternoon Also specials of she has
por la tarde También especiales de se ha
gone
vuelto
crazy
loca
to me that for me that won a point Let's
a mí eso para mí eso ganó un puntazo A
see you know that these people are many they are
ver tú sabes que esta gente son muchos
very sellouts and with the subject of Rocío
son muy vendidos y con el tema de Rocío
Carrasco we have seen many sellouts
Carrasco hemos visto muchos vendidos
but Paloma there was between the sword and
pero Paloma ahí estaba entre la espada y
the wall man
la pared tío
for example I do not value the
yo por ejemplo no valoro la
professionalism of one or I do not value there
profesionalidad de uno o no valora haya
all the opinions of all
todas las opiniones de todas las
people and the criteria for the Rocío
personas y el criterio por el tema Rocío
Carrasco issue, for example, a María Patiño Yes,
Carrasco por ejemplo una María Patiño Sí
because a María Patiño has
porque una María Patiño
lowered everything And you know, because of the
se ha bajado todo Y sabes por por el
Rocío Carrasco issue, she has lost everything,
tema Rocío Carrasco la ha perdido todo
but now, for example, there are other
pero ahora ya por ejemplo hay otros
journalists that I cannot
periodistas que los que yo no puedo
share the opinion But then maybe
compartir la opinión Pero luego a lo
other issues, of course,
mejor otros temas claro
because that's how it is, she has also lowered her
porque es así también se ha bajado los
pants and I'll tell you another thing, that with
pantalones y te digo otra cosa que lo de
Pepe Navarro, I think that
Pepe Navarro yo creo que
I think she did it because she found herself
yo creo que lo hizo porque se encontró
between a rock and a hard place because she
entre la espada y la pared porque ella
can't sell the image of super
no puede vender la imagen de súper
feminist Power and sit with Pepe
feminista Power y estar sentada con Pepe
Navarro, you know. So I think that there she
Navarro sabes Entonces yo creo que ahí
felt a little cornered and said,
se vio un poco arrinconada y dijo
by that rule of three, I said it the other
por esa regla de tres yo lo dije el otro
day, there is a person who went to testify
día hay una persona que fue a testificar
in favor of Pepe Navarro in a trial,
a favor de Pepe Navarro a un juicio
being a friend of his, and he with a sentence,
siendo amiga suya y él con una sentencia
a conviction for abuse, you
una condena por maltratada por maltrato
know, and he defends Rocío Carrasco, that
sabes y y defiende a Rocío carasco esa
person, and we all know who it is, and I'm not
persona y todos sabemos Quién es y ya no
going to name her anymore because I'm lazy,
la voy a nombrar más que me da pereza
but come on, there is a person who was that, I did
pero vamos hay una persona que fue eso
n't know, there is a person who went to
no sabía yo hay una persona que fue a
testify in favor of Pepe Navarro  Look, you'll
declarar a favor de Pepe Navarro Mira ya
see how people, you'll see, look, I'm going to
verás como la gente ya verás mira lo voy
say it, but you'll see, I
a decir pero ya verás
told it, yes, I told it in this live broadcast
lo conté sí lo conté en este directo la
last week, Javi, you pay very little attention to me, he
semana pasada Javi me haces poquísimo
went to testify as a witness
caso fue a declarar a favor como testigo
in favor of Pepe Navarro in the trial
a favor de Pepe Navarro en el juicio
against Ivonne Vale, then Ivo calls me
contra Ivonne Vale entonces ivo me llama
and tells me this person came, he was
y me dice ha venido esta persona estaba
present to testify in favor of Pepe
presente a declarar a favor de Pepe
Navarro and that person defends Rocío
Navarro y esa persona defiende a Rocío
Carrasco, however, he positioned himself
Carrasco sin embargo se posicionó en el
in favor of Pepe in the trial. Look,
juicio a favor de Pepe ya mira la gente
how people are writing. You see, people have
cómo está escribiendo Ya ves la gente si
found out. Look, you said it. They
se ha enterado Mira tú has dicho Aquí lo
are hitting the nail on the head here, everything said
están dando en el clavo todo lo dicho
here last week is like that. Look,
aquí la semana pasada así Mira están
everyone is hitting the nail on the head, eh,
dando en el clavo todos eh
I wouldn't forget something like that, Eh, yes, yes, yes, yes, no, no, no, no,
una cosa como esa no me olvidaría Eh sí
no. It really was here,
no no no no no no De verdad que fue aquí
eh. Look, everyone who is writing is hitting the nail on the head,
eh Mira andando en el clavo todos los
90%.   I'm
que están escribiendo el 90%.
going to check it out how strong What is
lo voy a revisar que fuerte a Qué es
strong is strong because so you can
fuerte es fuerte pues para ser para que
see the double standard and the
veas la doble vara de medir y los
interests, I mean here in this story there have
intereses o sea aquí en esta historia ha
been interests on all sides from one
habido intereses por todos lados de un
side of the opposition for all and that's it's that we
bando de oppo por todos la y ya está es
know how this works is that it's that
que sabemos cómo funciona esto es que es
in the end we believe that
que en fin luego nos creemos que
then you're not going to succeed on
entonces tú no vas a traer a triunfar en
TV Marina never no well you value
la tele Marina nunca no bueno valores
give me a few years give me a few years man
dame unos años dame unos años hombre a
maybe not on Telecinco but maybe you
lo mejor en telecinco no pero a lo mejor
value no because you're worth You're worth
valores no porque tú valgas Tú vales
well You're worth more than half of that
bueno Tú vales más que la mitad de ahí
too I'll tell you but I mean he
también te digo pero me refiero
never tells me anything nice I'm fed up since
nunca me dice nada bonito estoy harta ya
I'm more of the wild side
que soy más de la parte salvaje
and he challenged the one in the photo the other
y ha desafiado al de la foto del otro
day eh
día eh
to my best friend and people saying what a
a mi mejor amigo y la gente diciendo que
good couple Oh my Diego yes yes
buena pareja Ay mi Diego sí sí
[Music]
[Música]
start straight dancing and in the end you haven't
iniciar directo bailando y al final no
done any
lo has hecho
dancing anymore I'm already dancing anymore I don't
de bailes ya yo estoy de bailes ya yo no
want any more dancing no please what I
quiero yo más bailes no por favor
think is what we should do and
lo mío yo creo que deberíamos hacer y
I'm not even a youtuber Well still
eso que yo no soy youtuber Bueno todavía
no no no no no no no no but like we
no no no no no no no no no pero en plan
should  do as good you can't
deberíamos hacer como bueno no se puede
do as a joint live of everyone
hacer como un directo conjunto de todos
and as if everyone reconciles and
y como que todo el mundo se reconcilie y
everyone is
que todo el mundo le vaya
smart about life but there
lista de la vida pero
is one person with whom I am not going to
hay una persona con la que no voy a
share the screen
compartir pantalla
that I there is one person that I am not going to I don't
que yo hay una persona que no voy a no
wish bad on anyone but I do not share the
le deseo mal a nadie pero yo no comparto
screen
pantalla
myself For example I differentiate between
yo Por ejemplo yo se diferencia a los
personal problems and work no and I
problemas personales del trabajo no y yo
For example if I have to coincide in a
Por ejemplo si tengo que coincidir en un
place with a certain person but in a plan
sitio con cierta persona pero en plan
to debate like there is a debate
para debatir en plan que haya un debate
of people and have coincide with him to
de gente y tener coincidido con el para
give him saska the contrary has done I
darle saska al contrario ha hecho yo
know like no Oh no you don't know what I'm
sabes en plan no Ay no no sabes lo que
telling you no where this one is no I'm not going it
te digo no yo donde esté este no no voy
depends on what I
depende
say
que lo digo
friendly collaboration Like for example
colaboración amistosa Como por ejemplo
when
cuando
on Antonio David's Channel he did
en el Canal de Antonio David sí que me
tell me Hey do you mind if you're sad and
dijo Oye te importa que estés triste y
I told him no I'll go another day there I gave in
yo le dije no Yo voy otro día ahí cedí
because during
porque durante
But hey I'll leave you eh Marina big kiss to
Pero oye que os dejo eh Marina besazo a
that new one on vk
ese nuevo por vk
we're talking bye thanks
estamos hablando chao gracias
[Music]
[Música]